

Andres Inciarte

Full Stack Developer

Phone: 678-338-6427

Email: andresnew00@hotmail.com

Website:

https://andresnew00.github.io/PortfolioV.2.0/

Address

579 Northfield Ct, Lawrenceville GA 30045

Skills

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, React, React-Native, Mongodb , Firebase, MySQL, Node Js

I am a Full Stack developer with expertise on creating websites and applications that work, with strong leadership skills to make projects into finish products in the shortest amount of time and with guaranteed efficacy.

Experience

2018 - Present

Veterinary Technician La Vista Animal Hospital

2016 - 2018

Veterinary Assistant Lawrenceville Animal Care Center

2015 - 2016

Kennel Assistant Lawrenceville Animal Care Center

Education

Georgia Institute of Technology

Atlanta, Georgia Full Stack Web Development Certified

Projects

xBooks - https://xbooks-gt2018.herokuapp.com/

- A library manager prototype using Node, Express, Sequelize, GoogleBooks API, ESLint, and a variety of npm packages.

EnterVal – https://github.com/bshephe9/Enter-Val.git

- Manage your time for your troubles and your family. Whether it's making to help manage your time for addiction troubles or to manage your children's time, this app is perfect for every day and special case needs.



9